[
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 0",
        "front": "希",
        "back": "바랄 희"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 1",
        "front": "胡",
        "back": "나비 호"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 2",
        "front": "貝",
        "back": "조개 패"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 3",
        "front": "雖",
        "back": "비록 수"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 4",
        "front": "雙",
        "back": "두 쌍"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 5",
        "front": "茶",
        "back": "차 다"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 6",
        "front": "乃",
        "back": "이내 내"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 7",
        "front": "得",
        "back": "얻을 득"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 8",
        "front": "君",
        "back": "임금 군"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 9",
        "front": "斗",
        "back": "말 두"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 10",
        "front": "光",
        "back": "빛 광"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 11",
        "front": "丹",
        "back": "붉을 단"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 12",
        "front": "也",
        "back": "잇기 야"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 13",
        "front": "字",
        "back": "글자 자"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 14",
        "front": "舌",
        "back": "혀 설"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 15",
        "front": "且",
        "back": "또 차"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 16",
        "front": "宅",
        "back": "집 택"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 17",
        "front": "香",
        "back": "향기 향"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 18",
        "front": "不",
        "back": "아닐 불"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 19",
        "front": "馬",
        "back": "말 마"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 20",
        "front": "沐",
        "back": "머리감을 목"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 21",
        "front": "受",
        "back": "받을 수"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 22",
        "front": "而",
        "back": "말이을 이"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 23",
        "front": "飛",
        "back": "날 비"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 24",
        "front": "康",
        "back": "편안 강"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 25",
        "front": "李",
        "back": "오얏 리"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 26",
        "front": "巨",
        "back": "클 거"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 27",
        "front": "島",
        "back": "섬 도"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 28",
        "front": "弓",
        "back": "활 궁"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 29",
        "front": "豚",
        "back": "돼지 돈"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 30",
        "front": "丘",
        "back": "언덕 구"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 31",
        "front": "桑",
        "back": "뽕나무 상"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 32",
        "front": "信",
        "back": "믿을 신"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 33",
        "front": "妻",
        "back": "아내 처"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 34",
        "front": "泰",
        "back": "클 태"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 35",
        "front": "輿",
        "back": "수레 여"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 36",
        "front": "忍",
        "back": "참을 인"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 37",
        "front": "虎",
        "back": "범 호"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 38",
        "front": "見",
        "back": "볼 견"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 39",
        "front": "開",
        "back": "열 개"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 40",
        "front": "害",
        "back": "해할 해"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 41",
        "front": "狂",
        "back": "미칠 광"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 42",
        "front": "毛",
        "back": "터럭 모"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 43",
        "front": "白",
        "back": "흰 백"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 44",
        "front": "卵",
        "back": "알 란"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 45",
        "front": "笑",
        "back": "웃음 소"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 46",
        "front": "夕",
        "back": "저녁 석"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 47",
        "front": "誘導",
        "back": "유도"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 48",
        "front": "考試",
        "back": "고시"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 49",
        "front": "講義",
        "back": "강의"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 50",
        "front": "專攻",
        "back": "전공"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 51",
        "front": "工夫",
        "back": "공부"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 52",
        "front": "選拔",
        "back": "선발"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 53",
        "front": "投機",
        "back": "투기"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 54",
        "front": "機會",
        "back": "기회"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 55",
        "front": "運營",
        "back": "운영"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 56",
        "front": "和暢",
        "back": "화창"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 57",
        "front": "散步",
        "back": "산보"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 58",
        "front": "視力",
        "back": "시력"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 59",
        "front": "猛烈",
        "back": "맹렬"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 60",
        "front": "突進",
        "back": "돌진"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 61",
        "front": "抽出",
        "back": "추출"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 62",
        "front": "可能",
        "back": "가능"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 63",
        "front": "基盤",
        "back": "기반"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 64",
        "front": "期待",
        "back": "기대"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 65",
        "front": "經營",
        "back": "경영"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 66",
        "front": "直徑",
        "back": "직경"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 67",
        "front": "繼承",
        "back": "계승"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 68",
        "front": "歷史",
        "back": "역사"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 69",
        "front": "使命",
        "back": "사명"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 70",
        "front": "社會",
        "back": "사회"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 71",
        "front": "立脚",
        "back": "입각"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 72",
        "front": "完遂",
        "back": "완수"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 73",
        "front": "寄與",
        "back": "기여"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 74",
        "front": "複雜",
        "back": "복잡"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 75",
        "front": "適",
        "back": "맞을 적"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 76",
        "front": "歡",
        "back": "기쁠 환"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 77",
        "front": "重量",
        "back": "중량"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 78",
        "front": "普通",
        "back": "보통"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 79",
        "front": "華",
        "back": "빛날 화"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 80",
        "front": "治療",
        "back": "치료"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 81",
        "front": "方式",
        "back": "방식"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 82",
        "front": "世界",
        "back": "세계"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 83",
        "front": "分類",
        "back": "분류"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 84",
        "front": "人類",
        "back": "인류"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 85",
        "front": "空想",
        "back": "공상"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 86",
        "front": "民族",
        "back": "민족"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 87",
        "front": "自由自在",
        "back": "자유자재"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 88",
        "front": "役割",
        "back": "역할"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 89",
        "front": "地域",
        "back": "지역"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 90",
        "front": "交換",
        "back": "교환"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 91",
        "front": "圈",
        "back": "무리 권"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 92",
        "front": "輕率",
        "back": "경솔"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 93",
        "front": "訴訟",
        "back": "소송"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 94",
        "front": "葛藤",
        "back": "갈등"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 95",
        "front": "指摘",
        "back": "지적"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 96",
        "front": "混線",
        "back": "혼선"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 97",
        "front": "視線",
        "back": "시선"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 98",
        "front": "助長",
        "back": "조장"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 99",
        "front": "污染",
        "back": "오염"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 100",
        "front": "調節",
        "back": "조절"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 101",
        "front": "決定",
        "back": "결정"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 102",
        "front": "設定",
        "back": "설정"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 103",
        "front": "實質",
        "back": "실질"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 104",
        "front": "增加",
        "back": "증가"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 105",
        "front": "活用",
        "back": "활용"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 106",
        "front": "安全",
        "back": "안전"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 107",
        "front": "日本",
        "back": "일본"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 108",
        "front": "始作",
        "back": "시작"
    },
    {
        "id": "prv30 - 109",
        "front": "人間",
        "back": "인간"
    }
]